[The Old Story of Yu Hong]
[Episode 32]
You've been questioned all day.
Are you holding up okay?
Careful. It's hot.
Thank you.
All of this is standard procedure.
Don't overthink it.
Just be cooperative.
If you've missed or omitted something,
just tell me.
[Forensic Investigation Room]
Last month—
I forget which day—
I treated the cement factory's
sales managers to dinner,
after which, I went with them
to sing kareoke.
Three Eyes happened to be on duty
that night.
I saw him in the lobby.
We said hi to each other.
That was the last time we talked.
I understand.
You must be feeling awful right now.
You grew up with him,
and married his sister later.
Besides his mother and sister,
you are the closest to him.
If even you hadn't noticed
anything wrong with him,
then nobody else
would have.
I used to think of myself
as his best friend.
I loved his sister for many years.
This time, when I came back
from the forest farm,
I thought I'd return
after a few months' rest.
It was not until
I ran into Three Eyes did I know
that his sister had fallen severely ill.
I didn't marry her out of pity.
I truly loved her.
When we got married,
Three Eyes was the happiest of all.
He kept calling me Brother-in-Law.
It sounded...
so affectionate.
He is
foolishly honest
and slow on the uptake.
Later, when Chen Hong got pregnant
and Hao Jie went to Shanghai,
he finally found out
my affair with Chen Hong.
He blamed me.
He blamed me for betraying his sister.
But Chen Hong saved her life.
Given that, we both felt awkward
and uneasy when we met up again
thereafter.
Eventually, we cut off contact
with each other.
So where do you think
he can possibly be right now?
I'm also eager to know where he is.
I've never been able to reach his sister
since she went to Shanghai.
I really want to ask him
how she is doing now
and if she has been cured.
Here, sign this.
Any findings?
The forensic report is in.
The dagger is the murder weapon.
We've issued an arrest warrant.
We'll be leaving then.
[Wanted]
[Half a month ago]
Yang?
Sit down.
Yang,
open your mouth.
Open up.
What's this?
Chicken butt.
With poop on it.
This chicken
must have had diarrhea before it died.
Do you remember Mr. Ji,
your homeroom teacher who taught math?
You mean Baldy Ji!
That was Baldy Ji.
Yes, exactly.
His glasses were as thick
as the bottom of a beer bottle.
Right.
Oh my.
One time, you were caught smoking
in the restroom
by a teacher from another class.
Mr. Ji told you to get a parent
to the school,
or he wouldn't let you go home.
Yes.
So you asked me to pretend
to be your dad, right?
You were a real badass back then,
taller than me by a head.
I was.
You...
You asked a bulky fool...
What was his name?
Let me think.
To lend you his glasses.
He was called Four Eyes.
Yes!
He was nicknamed Four Eyes.
You borrowed glasses from Four Eyes,
put on a hat, and came to my school.
Once you got to Baldy Ji's office,
he began
lecturing you
and it went on for 30 minutes.
But you didn't dare to say a word.
I dared not speak out of fear
of having my cover blown.
You acted like you got a stroke,
just nodding all along.
Right.
Later on,
Baldy Ji got confused.
Finally, he asked you one last question.
He asked, "Whose father are you?"
He did.
What was your answer?
Say it. How did you answer him?
I said, "Mr. Ji,
I'm Three Eyes' father, named Four Eyes."
Because of you,
from that day on,
everyone started calling me Three Eyes.
What were you thinking?
The son of Four Eyes is called Three Eyes?
People still refer to me
as Three Eyes now.
Even hookers call me that.
And I have to invent a reason,
telling them that in a previous fight,
I was wounded
by knives, guns, and firepower.
That is complete nonsense.
This is all your fault.
How is your sister doing?
She underwent surgery.
It was a sucess.
Actually, my sister
didn't call me until a week
after her surgery.
I wasn't happy at all
when I answered the phone,
because I know my sister too well.
If the surgery had failed
after such a long time
she spent alone in Shanghai,
she would've had a mental breakdown.
So I got scared at the thought
that the phone call might be from someone
telling me to collect her body.
It's okay.
Everything will be fine.
Thank you, Brother-in-Law.
What "Brother-in-Law"?
I'm not your brother-in-law anymore.
You are my brother-in-law.
You treated my sister well.
In fact, I've known the entire time
that you got together
with Chen Hong just in order to
earn money for my sister's treatment.
I did hate you at first,
but my sister told me not to.
She said to me
that the money for her trip to Shanghai
and her surgery
was all from you.
And it was she who suggested a divorce.
You already
did your utmost by marrying her.
You didn't even learn Chinese well.
Stop using fancy phrases.
I'm serious, Brother-in-Law.
N-Nobody has treated my sister
better than you did.
You treated her better than anyone else.
Actually, I've kept one thing...
to myself for a long time.
My kidney turned out to be
a match for my sister's.
But I told her it wasn't.
When I tore up the test results,
do you know how terrible I felt?
I felt like I was a piece of trash.
My sister has always been nice to me
since we were little.
But I was scared.
I was just scared.
When we were kids,
my dad once
sent home a bag of White Rabbit candy
from Shanghai.
Every couple of days,
my sister and I would be
each given a piece.
But by the time
the whole bag was finished,
my sister hadn't eaten a single piece.
Then, my mom went mentally ill.
Even while my sister was on dialysis,
she still cooked for me.
But I was just so scared.
Sometimes I wonder
why must my sister
be the one who needs dialysis.
Why does she have
such a cowardly brother?
Why?
Everyone fears death.
I fear death too.
So sometimes, in order to live,
we have to let others die.